Guide to the Rose Cumming, Russell L. Cecil, and Affiliated Families Photographs and Papers 1870s-2012 PR 393
New-York Historical Society
Rose Cumming, Russell L. Cecil, and affiliated families photographs and papers
1870s-2012
New-York Historical Society
Cecil, Russell L. (Russell La Fayette), 1881-1965
Cumming, Rose, 1887-1968
PR 393
16 Linear feet in 13 boxes (7 record cartons and 6 flat boxes).
Family photographs, letters, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks, and ephemera documenting the lives and careers of Australian-American sisters Rose Stuart Cumming (1887–1968), a groundbreaking interior decorator; Dorothy Cumming (1894–1983), a silent film actress best known for playing the Virgin Mary in Cecil B. DeMille's "King of Kings" (1927); and Eileen Cumming Cecil (1892–1982), a writer, advertising executive, and designer, who married noted rheumatologist and medical textbook author Dr. Russell LaFayette Cecil (1881–1965). Of note are the photographs of interiors decorated by Rose Cumming, a scrapbook of Florsheim Shoes advertisements by Eileen Cumming Associates, and a booklet of production stills from "King of Kings." The collection includes a small group of textile samples made by Rose Cumming Chintzes that reproduces some of Rose's original floral designs.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in two series, each divided in four sub-series. Material within each sub-series is sorted alphabetically by document type or topic.
Series I. Cumming family photographs and papers, 1870s-2012
Sub-series I.A. Rose Stuart Cumming, 1890s-2012
Sub-series I.B. Dorothy (Cumming) (Elliott) McNab and husbands, 1915-1978
Sub-series I.C. Greville and Anthony Cumming (sons of Dorothy Cumming), 1920s-1970s
Sub-series I.D. Other Cumming and related families, 1870s-1943
Series II. Cecil family photographs and papers, 1872-2003
Sub-series II.A. Russell LaFayette Cecil, 1880s-1975
Sub-series II.B. Eileen Cumming Cecil, 1890s-1982
Sub-series II.C. Russell Cumming Cecil, 1920s-2003
Sub-series II.D. Other Cecil and related families, 1872-1986
Biographical / Historical
This collection centers on the lives and intertwined careers of three talented Australian-American sisters, Rose, Eileen, and Dorothy Cumming, daughters of sheep rancher Victor Cumming and his wife, Sarah (Fennell) (Hughes) Cumming, who arrived in the United States during the second decade of the twentieth century.
The eldest, and perhaps best known, Rose Stuart Cumming (1887–1968), became an interior decorator on the advice of Vanity Fair editor Frank Crowninshield. After an apprenticeship Rose opened her own shop in 1921, and was based for a long time at 515 Madison Avenue in Manhattan before moving to 499 Park Avenue six years before her death. At a time in the 1920s, '30s, and beyond, when tastes ran towards Louis XV and English Georgian antique furniture, her unorthodox use of chinoiserie, smoked mirrors, lacquered surfaces, and self-designed chintz fabrics drew such celebrity clients as the actresses Marlene Dietrich, Mary Pickford, and Norma Shearer. Rose displayed her best merchandise in her shop windows, which she left illuminated at night, a trick of salesmanship she is credited with pioneering.
The second sister, Eileen Cumming Cecil (1892–1982), was also attracted by interior decorating, and wrote on the subject for Vogue and House Beautiful, among other publications, where she often profiled—and advertised—her sister Rose's work. Adam Gimbel, of the Gimbel Brothers department store chain, tapped Eileen to design an elegant image for his company's Saks Fifth Avenue venture. She headed her own advertising firm, Eileen Cumming Associates, and for three years, beginning in 1933, managed advertising for Bonwit Teller. After her sister, Rose, died in 1968, Eileen assumed the presidency of Rose Cumming, Inc., and continued the fabric and antiques business with her granddaughter, Sarah Cumming Cecil. In 1923 Eileen married Dr. Russell LaFayette Cecil (1881–1965), a founder and president of the American Rheumatism Association (now American College of Rheumatology) and author of the widely-used Textbook of Medicine, first released in 1927 and now past its 25th edition. Eileen and Russell Cecil had one child, the architect Russell Cumming Cecil (1926–2009).
Dorothy (Cumming) (Elliott) McNab (1894–1983), the youngest of the Cumming sisters, was an actress and playwright best known for her portrayal of Mary, the mother of Jesus, in Cecil B. DeMille's 1927 epic "The King of Kings." Her play, "The Woman Brown," ran for eleven performances in December 1939 at New York's Biltmore Theatre. She was married and divorced twice, first to Frank Elliott Dakin (a.k.a. Frank Elliott), a stage director by whom she had two sons (who used their mother's maiden name): Greville C. E. Cumming (1922–1944) and Anthony F. Cumming (1924– ). Her second husband was Duncan Allan McNab (a.k.a. Allan McNab), a British artist and designer. Dorothy shared her sisters' penchant for finery, and established a business, Dorothy McNab Ltd.—"Fabulous Fabrics, Feminine Fashions"—at her home in Montego Bay, Jamaica.
_______________
Information on the Cumming sisters and Dr. Cecil is drawn from material in the collection and from their obituaries in the New York Times: "Dr. Russell Cecil, Arthritis Expert" (June 2, 1965); "Rose Cumming, 81, Decorator of 'Ancestral' Interiors, Dead" (March 23, 1968); "Eileen Cecil, Interior Decorator" (September 9, 1982); "Dorothy C. M'Nab" (December 31, 1983). For more on the family, their work and activities, see the copy of Jeffrey Simpson's 2012 book Rose Cumming: Design Inspiration, which has been annotated and corrected by Eileen's granddaughter, Sarah Cumming Cecil, in box 1, folder 13.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers by appointment only. The collection includes one motion picture film (Box 4, Folder 22) and two reels of audiotape (Box 5, Folders 14-15). These are restricted until they have been preservation reformatted. In any case, N-YHS lacks the equipment required to play them.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Sarah C. Cecil, 2019 (accession no. PPAC.2019.029).
Related Materials
The Mattie E. Hewitt & Richard A. Smith Photograph Collection, PR-26, includes images of interiors decorated by Rose Cumming (see Box 5, Folders 92-95).
Scope and Contents
The photographs, letters, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks, and ephemera in the present collection originated with four key, related individuals—the Cumming sisters Rose, Dorothy, and Eileen, and Eileen's husband, Dr. Russell L. Cecil. Eileen appears to have been the clan's unofficial record keeper, preserving material from her own and her husband's family. Although the collection spans the late nineteenth through the early twenty-first centuries, its coverage is woefully spotty. Diaries are fragmentary. Letters, especially those from Dorothy Cumming, are usually incomplete, lacking either their initial pages or subsequent sheets. Many photographs are unidentified and undated. The material overlaps from person to person in the way common to records of a close-knit family.
Of chief interest are the photographs of interiors decorated by Rose Stuart Cumming, a 1920s or '30s booklet advertising her specialties, and a guided tour/inventory of the contents of her residence at 36 West 53rd Street, which, like all of her homes, functioned as a showroom. Some youthful scrapbooks include doodles and more accomplished drawings, perhaps the beginnings of her artistic aspirations. Also present is a small group of textile samples, some with tags indicating they were produced by "Rose Cumming Chintzes," the company that succeeded Rose's business and reproduced her patterns. (See Sub-series I.A)
A booklet of publicity stills, and a number of photographs, show actress Dorothy Cumming costumed for her best-known role as the Virgin Mary in Cecil B. DeMille's 1927 silent epic "King of Kings." (See Sub-series I.B)
Letters and photographs from Dorothy's sons, Anthony "Tony" Cumming and Greville Cobbett Elliott Cumming document their time in the armed services during World War II, Tony in the U.S. Marines, and Greville in the King's Royal Rifle Corps of the British Army. Greville died, tragically, during the Battle of Anzio on February 28, 1944, when he was just twenty-one. A memorial booklet in the collection includes a biography of Greville by Vanity Fair editor Frank Crowninsheild. (See Sub-series I.C.)
The Cumming sisters' parents, Victor and Sarah (Fennell) (Hughes) Cumming, are represented by scattered letters, newspaper clippings, and photographs, as are Sarah's children by her first marriage, Marjorie (Hughes) Loney and Jack Hughes. (See Sub-series I.D.)
Beyond a few journal articles, and three folders of autobiographical material, the collection contains virtually none of Dr. Russell L. Cecil's professional writing. Most of his included letters and photographs are of a familial nature. Of interest to golf enthusiasts is a diary of Dr. Cecil's scores and performances kept between 1950 and 1963. (See Sub-series II.A.)
Similarly, the professional life of Dr. Cecil's wife, Eileen Cumming Cecil, is documented by a handful of items: tear sheets of interior decorating articles she wrote in the 1920s for House Beautiful and Vogue, and a miniature 1927 pamphlet entitled "The Place of the Fashion Magazine," which reprints the text of a lecture that she delivered for the Department of Fine Arts of New York University. A scrapbook gathers Florsheim Shoes advertisements publicized by her firm, Eileen Cumming Associates, probably in the 1930s. (See Sub-series II.B.)
Russell Cumming Cecil, son and only child of Dr. Russell L. and Eileen Cumming Cecil, was an architect, but the only item of professional interest among his scattered letters, photographs, and youthful school essays in the collection is a December 1972 House & Garden profile of a house he designed for Wilfred Cohen on Long Island Sound. Russell C. Cecil's son, Dr. Russell N. A. Cecil, corresponded in 1999 with Dr. James A. Pitman of the University of Alabama who was writing a paper on textbooks of internal medicine and sought to include information on Dr. Russell L. Cecil's 1927 Textbook of Medicine. (See Sub-series II.C.)
The extended Cecil family—Russell L. Cecil's parents, the Presbyterian minister Rev. Russell Cecil and his wife, Alma (Miller) Cecil; his siblings, John Howe Cecil Sr., James McCosh Cecil, Alma (Cecil) Cary, and Elizabeth (Cecil) Scott; and assorted nieces and nephews—are documented by scattered letters, photographs, and newspaper clippings. (See Sub-series II.D.)
Advertising -- Shoes; Interior decoration; King of Kings (Motion picture: 1927); Motion picture actors and actresses; Rheumatologists; Diaries.; Ephemera.; Human hair; Letters (correspondence).; Menus; Photographs.; Photograph albums.; Scrapbooks.; Cecil, Eileen Cumming, 1892-1982; Cecil, Russell L. (Russell La Fayette), 1881-1965; Cumming, Dorothy, 1894-1983; Cumming, Rose, 1887-1968; Cecil (Family); Cumming (Family)
- Series I. Cumming family photographs and papers, 1870s-2012
  Arrangement
  Series I is organized in four sub-series. Material within each sub-series is sorted alphabetically by document type or topic.
  Sub-series I.A. Rose Stuart Cumming, 1890s-2012
  Sub-series I.B. Dorothy (Cumming) (Elliott) McNab and husbands, 1915-1978
  Sub-series I.C. Greville and Anthony Cumming (sons of Dorothy Cumming), 1920s-1970s
  Sub-series I.D. Other Cumming and related families, 1870s-1943
  - Sub-series I.A. Rose Stuart Cumming, 1890s-2012
    Scope and Contents
    Sub-series I.A includes photographs, letters, newspaper clippings, and ephemera relating to interior decorator Rose Stuart Cumming (1887–1968). Of particular interest are the photographs of rooms she furnished (box 1, folders 26–27; box 8, folders 1–5), many of which came from deteriorated scrapbooks, where they were unidentified. A number, however, are reproduced in Jeffrey Simpson's 2012 book Rose Cumming: Design Inspiration, a copy of which may be found in box 1, folder 13. See, too, the vintage booklet "Rose Cumming, Designer of Interiors" (box 1, folder 14), Karl Freund's guided tour/inventory of "The Brownstone House of Rose Cumming, 36 West 53rd Street" (box 1, folder 15), and the Parke-Bernet Galleries 1968 auction catalog of her personal property (box 1, folder 11). The fabric samples in box 2 appear to originate with Rose Cumming Chintzes, a successor business that reproduced and marketed her designs.
    - Anzac Dinner, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Rose Cumming, with her sister, Eileen, under the auspices of the Anzac Division of the British War Relief Society, organized a dinner at the Waldorf-Astoria to mark Anzac Day in tribute to Australians and New Zealanders "who served and died in all wars, conflicts, and peacekeeping operations." ("ANZAC" stands for Australian and New Zealand Army Corps.) Contains correspondence, newspaper clippings, and five copies of the program/menu.
    - Article: Augusta Owen Patterson, "The Grand Manner in a Triplex," Town & Country, 1947 April (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Article: Rose Cumming, "A Door Always Open", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      A photocopy of Rose's chapter contributed to The Finest Rooms, By America's Great Decorators (New York: Viking Press, 1964).
    - Article: Jeffrey Simpson, "Rose Cumming Chintzes -- Honoring the Past," New York Times Magazine, 1980 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Article: David Grafton, "Cafe Society: When Going Out Was Great", [1987?] (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Photographs by Jerome Zerbe, a friend of Cumming girls, according to a note on the article.
    - Article: Mark Hampton, "Grandes Dames of Decorating," House & Garden, 1990 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Article: Jared Du Pont Goss, "Designing Women," Decor, 1995 April / May (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Article: Arthur Lubow, "Arbus Reconsidered," New York Times Magazine (2 copies), 2003 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Rose Cumming's name is visible in photograph of Diane Arbus appointment book from 1959 (p. 40).
    - Article: John Esten, "Park Avenue Rose," Quest, 2005 March (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Article: Linda E. Clopton, "By Any Other Name: Rose Cumming, Ltd., American Beauty", undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Auction catalog, 1968 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Parke-Bernet Galleries catalog of "English & Continental Eighteenth Century Furniture & Other Decorative Furniture, Old Master Paintings, Decorations, The Personal Property of the Late Rose Cumming."
    - Book: John Kobler, Otto the Magnificent: The Life of Otto Kahn (New York: Charles Scribner's Sons), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Kobler dispells the rumor that Rose Cumming was Otto Kahn's mistress.
    - Book: Jeffrey Simpson, Rose Cumming: Design Inspiration (Rizzoli), 2012 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      With an introduction by Rose's grandniece and business successor, Sarah Cumming Cecil (granddaughter of Eileen Cumming Cecil), who has annotated and corrected this copy.
    - Booklet: "Rose Stuart Cumming, Designer of Interiors", [1920s-1930s] (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "The Brownstone House of Rose Cumming, 36 West 53rd Street", [1960?] (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Multiple copies of Karl Freund's guided tour / inventory of Rose Cumming's residence.
    - Chinese paper mats, undated (Box 12 (flat), Folder 1)
      Colorful paper mats, perhaps originally intended for spiritual devotions, from a folder marked "Rose made placemats from these -- bought in Chinatown, NYC."
    - Ephemera, 1899-1942, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Fabric samples, 1978, undated (Box 2)
      Nine fabric samples, some with tags for "Rose Cumming Chintzes" (one bears a copyright date of 1978), and seven small, striped slipcovers or antimacassars.
    - Letters, 1905-1912 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Letters from "Gilbert", 1912-1913, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Letters, 1913-1920 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Letters, 1921-1928 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Letters, 1933-1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Letters (undated) (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Letters of condolence to sister, Eileen Cumming Cecil, 1968 February-March (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1926-1979, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Printing plate: "Rose Cumming" stationery, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Printing plate with facsimile signature of Rose Cumming, 515 Madison Avenue, Specialist in Decoration, Antiques, Bibelots, Reproductions of Antique Wallpapers and Chintzes. Materials Wholesale and Retail.
    - Photographs, interiors (scrapbook) (2 folders), undated (Box 8 (flat), Folder 1-2)
    - Photographs, interiors (loose) (2 folders), undated (Box 8 (flat), Folder 3-4)
      Includes images by Mattie Edwards Hewitt, more of which may be found in the New-York Historical Society's Mattie E. Hewitt & Richard A. Smith Photograph Collection, PR-26.
    - Photographs, interiors: Cecil residence, 535 Park Avenue, undated (Box 8 (flat), Folder 5)
    - Photographs, interiors: Cecil residence, 153 East 61st Street (magazine tear sheets), [1930s?] (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Related Materials
      See also the blueprints for this residence in sub-series II.A, box 13 (flat), folder 1.
    - Photographs, interiors: Rose Cumming shop, East 59th Street (transparencies), 1978-2008 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Bill Kontzias, photographer, "R. Cumming transparencies of original shop in NYC Fine Arts Building, East 59th Street."
    - Photographs: "Green Shutters," South Main Street, Southampton, New York, undated (Box 8 (flat), Folder 6)
    - Photographs: 499 Park Avenue (location of Rose Cumming shop), 1978 April 3 (Box 12 (flat), Folder 2)
    - Photographs, personal, circa 1905-1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Photographs, personal, undated (Box 8 (flat), Folder 7)
    - Portrait (charcoal), undated (Box 12 (flat), Folder 3)
    - Portrait (pastel), 1923 (Box 13 (flat), Folder 2)
      Framed, oval, pastel portrait of Rose Cumming by Jean Eritziane (1850-1925).
    - Portrait (watercolor), undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Conditions Governing Access
      This portrait survives in multiple, fragile pieces. Handle with care.
    - Rose Cumming, Inc., 1920s-1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Scrapbook, [1890s] (Box 7, Enclosure 1 (folder 1))
    - Scrapbook, 1897-1906 (Box 7, Enclosure 1 (folder 2))
    - Scrapbook, 1906-1912 (Box 9 (flat), Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1913-1918 (Box 9 (flat), Folder 2)
  - Sub-series I.B. Dorothy (Cumming) (Elliott) McNab and husbands, 1915-1978
    Sub-series I.B includes letters, photographs, newspaper clippings, and ephemera relating to Dorothy (Cumming) (Elliott) McNab (1894–1983) and her husbands, Frank Elliott and Allan McNab. A number of photographs, and a booklet of publicity stills, depict Dorothy, a silent film actress, in costume for her most famous role as Mary, mother of Jesus, in Cecil B. DeMille's 1927 epic "King of Kings." Note that many of the letters Dorothy wrote to her sister, Eileen Cumming Cecil, and to her sons, are incomplete, either missing their final or initial pages. Some carry London addresses, where she lived for a time, or the imprint of her business in Jamaica, Dorothy McNab Ltd., "Fabulous Fabrics, Feminine Fashions."
    - Diary, 1944 January (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Diary (project diary), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Ephemera, 1910s-1930s (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Includes an illustrated booklet for Cecil B. DeMille's production of "The King of Kings" (1927) and playbill for Dorothy Cumming's play, "The Woman Brown," opening at the Biltmore Theatre, December 11, 1939.
    - Letters received, 1915-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Letters to sister, Eileen Cumming Cecil, 1936, 1970-1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Letters, etc. to sister, Eileen Cumming Cecil re: financial difficulties, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Letters to sister, Rose Cumming, 1925-1945, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Letters to son, Anthony "Tony" Cumming, 1938, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Letters to unidentified recipients, 1916-1961, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1920s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, miscellaneous, 1920s-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, personal, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, personal (oversize), 1917, [1927] (Box 10 (flat), Folder 1)
    - [1st husband] Frank Elliott (a.k.a. Frank Elliott Dakin). Telegram, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - [2nd husband] Allan McNab (a.k.a. Duncan Allan McNab). Letter and newspaper clippings, 1932, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - [2nd husband] Allan McNab (a.k.a. Duncan Allan McNab). Photographs, personal, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sub-series I.C. Greville and Anthony Cumming (sons of Dorothy Cumming), 1920s-1970s
    Sub-series I.C includes letters, photographs, and other material relating to the sons of Dorothy (Cumming) (Elliott) McNab: Anthony "Tony" Cumming (1924– ) and Greville Cobbett Elliott Cumming (1922–1944). Tony served in the U.S. Marines during World War II. Greville, a survivor of polio who became a lieutenant in the King's Royal Rifle Corps of the British Army, was killed during the Battle of Anzio, Italy, on February 28, 1944.
    - Greville Cumming. Letters, 1934, 1942-43, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Greville Cumming. Memorial booklet (2 copies), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Greville Cumming. Photographs, personal, [1920s-1944] (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Greville Cumming. Photographs, personal (oversize), undated (Box 10 (flat), Folder 2)
    - Greville Cumming. School: St. George's School, The Dragon, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Two issues containing work by Greville Cumming:
      Vol. 41, no. 3 (February 22, 1939): "To Iconoclasts" [poem]; "Le Fin" [fiction]
      Vol. 41, no. 4 (March 15, 1939): "Glory" [fiction]; "When Others Boasting" [poem]; "Despair" [poem]; ""Through the Night of Dark and --" [fiction]; "Great Contemporaries by Winston Churchill" [book review]
    - Greville Cumming. School: Princeton University. Dedication of World War II Panels in the Memorial Room of Nassau Hall, 1949 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Anthony "Tony" Cumming. Letters to aunt, Eileen Cumming Cecil, [1940s], 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Anthony "Tony" Cumming. Letters to aunt, Rose Cumming, [1940s-1950s], undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Anthony "Tony" Cumming. Letters to mother, Dorothy (Cumming) McNab, [1940s] (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Anthony "Tony" Cumming. Photographs, personal and family, [1940s-1970s] (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Anthony "Tony" Cumming. Photographs and negatives, "Tony & Greville", undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Sub-series I.D. Other Cumming and related families, 1870s-1943
    Sub-series I.D includes photographs and other material related to Victor Albert Cumming (1858–1926) and Sarah (Fennell) (Hughes) Cumming (c. 1860–1939), parents of Rose, Eileen, and Dorothy Cumming. Victor's sister, Agnes (Cumming) Harrison, is represented by photographs. And Sarah Cumming's children by her first marriage to Frederick Hughes—Marjorie (Hughes) Loney and Jack Hughes—are represented by letters, newspaper clippings, and photographs.
    - Sarah (Fennell) (Hughes) Cumming. Obituaries, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Sarah (Fennell) (Hughes) Cumming. Photographs, personal, 1870s-1930s (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Sarah (Fennell) (Hughes) Cumming. Photographs, personal (oversize), 1920s (Box 10 (flat), Folder 3)
    - Victor Cumming. Miscellaneous, 1889-1915 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Victor Cumming. Obituaries, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Victor Cumming. Photographs, personal, 1920s, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Victor Cumming. Photographs, personal (oversize), [1920s] (Box 10 (flat), Folder 4)
    - Agnes (Cumming) Harrison. Photographs, personal, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Jack Hughes. Letters, 1943, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Jack Hughes. Photographs, personal, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)